chobots.com 2009-11-29

# Chobots.com - Your Family Game!

This privacy policy sets out how Vayersoft LLC uses and protects any information that you give us while using chobots.com. We ensure that our privacy policy and information practices adhere to the United States Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

Chobots.com is an online world where kids and their parents can have fun, get entertained and make friends. We in Vayersoft LLC are committed to making this family environment safe and pleasant. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in compliance with this privacy statement. 

Vayersoft LLC may change this policy from time to time by updating the website. In case of such changes you will receive an email notification.

## The information we collect

We do not ask for any personally identifiable information from users who are under 13 years old. User accounts may only be registered by adults. Kids accounts are created by their parents. When registering with Chobots we ask that you NOT use your real name as your username.

To respond to a kids one-time request, we only ask for a valid parents email while the screen name is generated automatically.

We also require registration by age group in order to comply with federal guidelines for protecting children younger than 13 years of age. If a child selects a age group indicating that he/she is under 13, we require a parent's email address through which we notify the parent that his/her child has registered at our site as required under COPPA.

We enable users to chat online through our website, but all of our chat rooms are strictly monitored with a variety of security provisions. A chat filtering system automatically blocks personal information such as phone numbers and home addresses. An additional level of protection is guaranteed by Vayersoft employees who are constantly monitoring the chat.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new games, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. If we sell all or part of our business or make a sale or transfer of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer personally identifiable information to a third party as part of that transaction, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

All in all, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

## Controlling your and your child’s personal information

You may choose to change or delete your and your child’s personal information at any time by sending an email to support@chobots.com.

Also, you may want to enable safe chat for your child where s/he can only use a limited pictorial vocabulary.

## Inquiries concerning our privacy policies

All inquiries concerning the privacy policies of chobots.com should be directed to Vayersoft LLC
